# FANDA ALFARIDZI | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Jakarta, Indonesia | fanda.alvaridzi@gmail.com | +6281268120488 | LinkedIn | GitHub

#### **SUMMARY**

A Programmer with 2 years of industry **experience**, holding a Diploma in Informatics Management from Politeknik Negeri Padang. Specializes in developing and enhancing mobile and desktop applications. Skilled in designing, building, and maintaining efficient systems, with strong analytical abilities and a solution-oriented approach to meet business and technical needs.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **ORBIT ACADEMY**

Jakarta, Indonesia

Cloud Practitioner

October 2024 - December 2024

#### POLITEKNIK NEGERI PADANG

Padang, Indonesia

D3 Informatic Management

September 2020 - August 2023

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PT LINKIT 360

Jakarta, Indonesia

IT Developer

*May 2024 - Now* 

- ❖ Create automatic backups for transaction log partners on the server
- Developing an application dashboard
- ❖ Monitoring the server and troubleshooting
- System integration with partner system
- Indonesian and overseas Telco integration

#### **HPY Solution Indonesia**

Jakarta, Indonesia

Fullstack Dev

January 2024 - May 2024

- Creating e-inventory with scanner
- **❖** ERP Development
- Creating a new look for ERP with Vue Js

#### Jasamedika Saranatama

Jakarta, Indonesia

Fullstack Dev

January 2023 - August 2023

- Develop SIMRS (Hospital Management Information System) application modules in accordance with client requests
- Training users in the field to use SIMRS
- ❖ Creating reports for EMR (Electronic Medical Record) client based on client needs
- Installation of laundry module in hospital
- ❖ Adding electronic signature for doctor user

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Language: JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Dart, Go, C#, Python, BashScript,

Java, Kotlin SQL, HTML, CSS

**Frontend**: jQuery, Tailwind, Bootstrap, React Js, Next Js, Vue Js

**Mobile** : Flutter, Get X, React Native

Backend : Redis, Laravel, Code Igniter, Node Js, Express Js, Gin, Asp .Net, Docker
Database : MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQL Server, Mongo DB, Firebase, Supabase, SQLite
Server/Cloud : Aws, Gcp, Nginx, Docker, Cron, Grafana, Prometheus, Mimir, Loki, Tempo
Tools : Expo, Metro, Vercel, Docker, Cron, Dbeaver, Jira, Postman, Figma, Axios

#### **PROJECT**

## 1. Vision Z (Endoskopi Software)

Software for taking images of endoscopy equipment as well as for creating patient reports.

Tech: Java, SQLite

# 2. Perhompedin

Tech: Laravel, MySQL, Cron, GraphQL

### 3. Movie App

a mobile application that displays data on films currently showing in cinemas and those to be released

Tech: React Native, Axios, Expo

# 4. Weather App

a mobile app that knows the weather today and in the future.

Tech: JavaScript, React Native, Axios, Expo

## 5. RSVP

Digital wedding invitation web to invite guests easily

Tech: Laravel, Vue, Nginx, MySQL, VPS (Virtual Private Server)

# 6. Delisa Bakery

mini erp which includes an inventory module, manage employees and posts.

Tech: Code Igniter, MySQL

## **CERTIFICATION**

- 1. Cloud Practitioner AWS Orbit Academy
- 2. Mobile Dev React Native Progate Digitalent FGA
- 3. Machine Learning Dicoding
- 4. Junior Developer Kominfo/BNSP